[LARA] Prince.
Prince...
[hums]
Is this one really the prince?
Did you say something?
I need to know as much as I can
about the prince.
About the prince?
What do you mean, the prince?
[sighs]
Something like crystal clear
eyes that draw you in.
So, when you say the prince,
do you mean dark eyes
like a tall beast?
Beautiful silky hair
blowing in the wind?
A big muscular body.
Stop talking about me.
[sighs] Tests...
[LARA] I wonder what a prince
is really like now.
[♪ opening music begins]
[♪ opening music ends]
It has now been 3 whole weeks
since I came back
to the human world
and arrived in this town.
But yet, after all this time,
I still haven't been able
to find true love.
You've been glued to that
television day in and day out.
What on earth are you doing?
I'm learning everything about
the real world.
Oh, forget about that.
Go out there
and find true love already.
Well, yes,
I'd love to do that as well.
-Although...
-Although?
Mari, can you take me
to school today?
No way.
Mari, can you take me
to school today?
No chance.
-Mari, take me to school.
-No way.
[LARA] School...?
[WITCH] So, you haven't done
anything at all?
-It's because Mari...
-Why school?
-Why is it so important?
-It's the only place I know
where there are
lots of people gathering.
If I take you,
will you keep quiet?
Yes, of course!
All right,
but this is a one-time thing.
Okay.
Oh, wow!
It's time!
I'm finally going
to find my prince!
[WITCH] Lara...
Don't say anything you shouldn't
while you're out there.
Leave it to me.
-Make sure you act like a human.
-Leave it to me.
You mustn't say anything
about me or your situation.
Do you understand?
Not unless you want your tongue
cut out again like last time,
you hear?
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[MARI] We've gotta go.
It's been three weeks
since Lara moved in.
School, school, school.
It's all she asks about.
But it's exam season and there
aren't any clubs, so it's fine.
At least that's what I thought.
I regretted my decision
straight away.
Why did I think it was a good
idea to take her to school?
Do you think
there is a prince out there
who loves me and will make
everything back to normal again?
-I don't know.
-I have to find it though.
I have to find true love.
Knock it off.
I guess the question is,
what even is true love anyway?
Do you know, Mari?
If you say another word,
I'm leaving you behind.
But why?
Anyway,
regardless of what it is,
it's my destiny
to find true love.
[MARI] Shut up.
As if I care
about something like that.
Something like that?
I just don't want
to hear about it.
I don't even understand it.
Oh, there it is again.
There, can't you see that?
How many times
do I have to tell you?
-Well, that's weird.
-You're the one who's weird.
[LARA] It's school!
At last, the search
for my prince is about to begin!
-[grunts]
-Oh!
Hey, Mari,
where are you taking me to?
I have to go and find my prince.
He's here somewhere.
[gasps]
[♪ upbeat music]
[♪ music continues]
[thud]
[MARI] The exam
will be over by noon,
so wait here until then.
What's an exam?
Cross this line
and you're banned
from watching TV for life.
For life?
[door slams]
-[FEMALE] Lara?
-[MALE] Yes, I found her.
That's a relief.
So where is she?
Is Lara okay?
[MALE] Well, Lady Lara's fine,
but she has human legs.
[gasps]
That witch.
[sighs]
I wonder how much longer
I have to stay here.
-[YOSHIYA] Aw, man.
-Huh?
Oh, Yoshiya!
Lara?
What are you doing here?
-What's with the uniform?
-I'm waiting here for Mari.
Shouldn't you be studying
for that exam as well?
Ah, whatever. I don't care.
I'll never gonna leave
this town.
You know what you want,
don't you?
-Yeah, that's right.
-That's wonderful.
Why?
Because it means
you have conviction.
I think that's wonderful.
Uh...
Anyway,
what are you doing here again?
I wanted to come here
so I could find a prince.
A prince, huh?
You mean a boyfriend?
You can leave it to me.
I'll introduce you to some
guys from school.
[laughs]
Hey, is the test over already?
Yoshiya, the teacher
was looking for you earlier.
-Wait a minute, who's that girl?
-Don't worry about that.
I wanna know, who do you think
is the prince of our school?
The prince of our school?
Yeah, it's fine if it's me.
[girl sighs]
I can't think of anyone,
not at this school.
-[GIRL 1] What about this?
-[YOSHIYA] An idol?
-[GIRL 2] This one is my prince.
-[YOSHIYA] A comedian?
-[GIRL 3] This one is mine.
-[YOSHIYA] A VTuber?
There's no way you can
actually date any of them.
I just like to admire
my favorite idol.
It's not always about
going on dates.
Yeah, I don't wanna risk
fighting or being betrayed.
But it doesn't beat
the real thing though.
Who do you think
is the most popular at school?
It's fine if it's me.
Isn't the most popular guy
Ouji Moriyama?
Ouji?!
Yeah, but I think Ouji
is already seeing Himeka.
-Hime!
-Oh, that's them over there.
[gasps]
[LARA] The prince and the...
...princess.
-Huh?
-Oh, hey, Otsu!
-I've been looking for you.
-See you later.
Okay, bye.
-[LARA] Um...
-Huh?
-Can I help you?
-I wonder...
can you tell me
how you met your prince?
His name is Ouji Moriyama.
He's not a real prince,
but he does act
like royalty sometimes.
I don't mind.
My name is Himeka Maibara.
So cool!
I can't believe
that you two met.
I was born on the same day
at the same hospital as Ouji.
Our families
have always been really close
and looked out for each other.
-Oh...
-That makes total sense.
-It was fate, wasn't it?
-Not at all.
Do you have more things in
common with each other?
Mm...
Oh, we do have matching moles
on our arms.
It's right here.
I don't have one on my arm,
so then that must mean
it's definitely fate!
Yeah. You know,
you're really funny, Lara.
So have you both already
exchanged engagement rings yet?
[gasps]
[laughs]
What are you talking about?
We're just childhood friends.
There's nothing romantic
about us.
So, you mean to say
you both don't love each other?
Oh!
You two are so perfect together.
I just thought
you must be madly in love.
I guess you could say
we are closer
than just regular friends.
He's been by my side
ever since we were little,
and he's helped me out
quite a lot too.
He helped you a lot?
Well, it was nothing major,
like eating the food
I couldn't finish myself,
or when he would carry me
on his back when I hurt my leg.
Stuff like that.
[♪ gentle music]
Your Highness, you really
shouldn't be doing that.
Oh, I see.
So you've fallen for him?
No way! Everyone's always
jumping to the conclusion
that we're in love.
I'd be happy if we could just
stay on good terms like this
as best friends forever.
-Just like this forever?
-Sure.
I'd be fine if things with Ouji
stayed exactly as they are now.
-But that's impossible.
-Huh?
[LARA] It's bound
to come to an end someday.
I know.
Lara, you're definitely
not a student
at this school, are you?
So who was it
who brought you here?
-Huh?
-Oh, Mari!
-No more TV!
-[gasps]
But I got out
through the window!
[MARI] Same difference.
[HIME] Are you leaving already?
It'd be good to see you again.
I won't bring her here again.
Mari, where do you live?
-Ishiyama.
-Great, me too!
We can all walk together.
Hey, isn't that Ouji over there?
Wow, Lara,
you've got good eyesight.
Ouji said he was going home
with his friend but...
I'm gonna walk home with him.
Bye, see you later.
Lara, are you coming?
-[OUJI] Shall we go?
-Yeah.
[laughing]
What is this?
It's so tasty! No way!
-How can I ever repay you?
-It's totally fine.
-You don't need to do anything.
-Are you kidding?
I learned so much
from what you told me today.
[HIME] Oh, like what exactly?
[LARA] Well, you see,
I'm looking for my prince.
[HIME] Your prince?
Oh, but I don't mean
your prince.
I'm looking for my soulmate,
the one with whom
I can feel true love.
But it's so difficult.
I mean, you and Ouji,
on the other hand,
you both look like you are
truly meant for each other.
Hey, Himeka...
-Oh...
-[Himeka sobs]
So, Lara, the thing is,
I lied to you earlier today.
I lied because I really do...
like Ouji.
[gasps]
It's impossible!
There's no way I can love you!
No, wait!
That's so lame.
Some are loved by the prince
and it's wonderful,
and some aren't
and it's painful.
[crying]
It's not fair! Why should those
who are in love fight too?
Well, if you're that sensitive,
everything you watch
must be entertaining.
[TV] I have no choice
but to go back.
My 100 fiancées on my home
planet are waiting for me.
[FEMALE] Even so, life without
you is no life at all.
[MALE] I guess...
I love you!
[crying]
-[LARA] Mari.
-[MARI] What?
Can I go to school with you
again tomorrow, please?
[MARI] No way.
-[LARA] Pretty please?
-[MARI] Pretty no.
Mari...
[MARI] Hmm?
Lara, if you take this potion,
you can become human.
But before that,
I'm going to take your voice.
My voice?
The world above
is so very harsh and fragile.
Just a single word
in the wrong place,
and they will cast you out
without a second thought.
Oh, don't worry.
I'll give you your voice back
when the time comes.
Someday.
[♪ melancholic music]
[indistinct chatter]
Huh?
Lara?
If I admitted I liked Ouji,
I feel like it would ruin
my friendship with him,
so I just ignore my feelings
and pretend.
Although if our friendship
will end, then I'm going to wish
that I'd just admitted it
to him sooner.
Why not try now?
[sighs] It's impossible.
Ouji and I will never end up
together in that way.
Although sometimes you'll find
the impossible happens.
[♪ gentle piano music]
What's your name?
[gasps]
Quite strange...
but I feel like we've met
each other before somewhere.
Could this be fate?
Your feelings must have
gotten through to him.
[LARA] From then on,
that person became
someone very special to me.
Even without any words...
we could understand each other.
That's what I thought.
That's what you thought?
There's a reason
I came to see you today.
I had something I really wanted
to say to you.
I know this might be
none of my business,
but I think
that you should tell Ouji
exactly how you feel about him.
[gasps]
But why?
[LARA] I don't want you
to have any regrets because
I couldn't tell my prince one
thing I really wanted to say.
Now it's too late.
There is no way I can ever see
that person anymore.
Although you still can.
You can still see your prince.
I can't just tell him.
There's no way.
Are we done talking now?
Mari!
Look at you both.
Don't make those weird faces
while sitting
in front of my club room.
-Huh?
-[MARI] It's bad luck.
Mari...
Club activities
start tomorrow and I-—
[laughs]
[HIME] I'm sorry, Lara.
You were right all along.
I guess I have to tell Ouji
after all.
[OUJI] So...
Himeka,
you're like family to me.
You mean so much to me,
even if I don't love you
romantically.
I hope... you understand.
[crying]
[LARA] It's okay, go ahead
and cry your heart out.
-You're the only one crying.
-[HIME] Lara, it's okay, really.
In fact, it's amazing.
I already feel so much better.
[LARA] Better?
It's because I know he's not
the only prince out there.
[gasps]
I really can't wait
to meet a new prince,
and I will one day.
I'm so glad
you came back to see me today.
Thank you.
And thank you
to your friend Mari.
Hmm?
You are friends, aren't you?
[♪ gentle music]
Mm-hmm.
[HIME] Oh, Lara, please come
and visit me anytime.
[laughs]
He's not the only prince
out there.
I think that's really nice.
[MARI] You're so easily
influenced.
I wonder
when it'll happen to me.
When will I find my prince?
Well, right now you're looking
for fresh clams.
-[MARI] That one?
-Nope.
-This one?
-Perfect.
You're an expert.
Today's been so full
of my favorite things.
We're having okonomiyaki
tonight.
-[LARA] With fish?
-With meat.
Oh, I forgot to buy pork.
-I can go and get some.
-Uh...
-[MARI] You sure?
-I've got this.
[MARI] Right. Okay, thanks.
[laughs]
[panting]
Thank you. Come back soon.
Lady Lara.
Who are you?
It is really good to see you
once again, Lady Lara.
We met a very long time ago.
It was at the castle of
the Guardian of the Sea,
Lord Rowan.
[gasps]
Who are you? How do you
know my father's name?
Please tell me.
I go by the name Kota.
I have come here at the behest
of your older sister, Lady Lisa.
Lisa.
Although she isn't here today,
however,
she does want to talk to you.
So here she is.
[LISA] Lara.
[gasps]
[LARA] Big sis!
[♪ closing music begins]
[♪ closing music ends]
[LARA] Big sis!
Big sis!
[LISA] Lara, I'm so happy
to hear your voice
and to know
that you're back in the world.
[LARA] Where'd you go?
[crying] Home? Father? Everyone?
What happened to you all?
Lara, calm down.
The only ones awake
in this world right now
are you, me,
and Kota over there.
I want to see you, big sis!
I want to see you too,
but not right now.
[LARA] Why not?
[LISA] It's because...
I'm still very far away.
But I have so much I want
to tell you and fill you in on.
So don't worry, I'll definitely
be coming to see you soon.
You're my special princess,
little sis.
Don't forget.
[disconnect tone]
Big sis!
[MARI] Lara!
[LARA] That was definitely
my big sister's voice.
I didn't fully understand it
at the time,
why she hadn't come
to see me in person.
But anyway, that day
was full of happy things.
We had okonomiyaki for dinner.
Mari told me
that she was my friend...
...and my sister.
Big sis was alive!
I have no doubt at all.
That was Lara's voice.
I can't wait to eat.
[LISA] She was definitely
my beloved little sister.
Oh, I can help.
Hold on.
[groans]
[car horn honks]